

MONIR KHAN SHIMUL

Data-Driven Digital Marketer

+8801758379556

adnanshimul10@gmail.com

github.com/adnanshimul10

1205 Dhanmondhi.. Dhaka

EDUCATION

BSc in Computer Science Green University of Bangladesh 2020 - 2024

SKILLS TRAINING

Digital Marketing

Creative IT Institute 2021

Data-Driven Digital Marketing Skillupper 2021

Master in Digital Marketing Udemy 2022

SKILLS

SEARCH ENGINE OPTIMIZATION (SEO)

SOCIAL MEDIA MARKETING (SMM)

GOOGLE TAG MANAGER

GOOLE ANALYTICS 4

ENHANCE E-COMMERCE TRACKING

FACEBOOK CONVERSION API

FACEBOOK ADS

GOOGLE ADS

GOOGLE REMARKETING

EVENTS SETUP & TRACKING

FORM TRACKING

COOKIE CONSENT MODE V2 - GDPR FACEBOOK SERVER SIDE TRACKING

CONVERSION RATE OPTIMIZATION (CRO)

MACHINE LEARNING

ABOUT ME

Skilled in web analytics 4 and tracking setup, specializing in GA4, GTM, Google Tag Manager, and Consent Mode v2. Expert in Facebook Ads for sales and lead campaigns and tracking data using GA4, and Google Ads for conversion tracking and remarketing.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data-Driven Digital Marketing Specialist Bear My Brand | Dhaka

2021 - 2022

Experienced at Bear My Brand - As a Data-Driven Digital Marketing Specialist, worked with Google Analytics to track website traffic and campaign performance, Google Tag Manager for efficient tag management, Faceboo Conversion API for maximizing ROI, and adeptly manage Google and Faceboo Ads campaigns for target audience reach and marketing goals.

Digital Marketing Expert

June 2022 - February 2024

Attrock | India

Experienced at Attrock - Digital Marketing Agency:

Google Analytics: Analyzed traffic, tracked behavior, and generated reports. Google Tag Manager: Developed tag strategies, automated processes, and maintained structured tracking. Facebook Conversion API: Installed tracking, and optimized campaigns. Google Ads: Managed campaigns, conducted keyword research, optimized bids. Facebook Ads: Crafted engaging ads, utilized segmentation, conducted A/B tests.

Digital Marketing Mentor - 4 Batch Per Week

August 2022 - Till Now

Dreamland IT & Software | Dhaka

As a mentor at Dreamland IT and Software, I teach in Digital Marketing core skills -> Google Analytics, Google Tag Manager, Facebook Conversion API, Google Ads, and Facebook Ads to students, empowering them with essential digital marketing skills.

LANGUAGES

FNGLISH FRENCH - CONVERSATIONAL **GERMANY - CONVERSATIONAL**

MARKETING PORTFOLIO



https://drive.google.com/file/d/1yIvDnxzB m6wN3sYPI-YhIP9ytQs80Hs8/view? usp=sharing